Yeah.
Yeah the
or
. Law or.
A reality.
Yeah. Yeah
alright yeah
or.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah
a little A or. Lol
. LOL
LOL off. The or the
little naughty little.
Was.
So so. So so. So so.
Excited.
You got it wrong number. Sky.
Pixie. Sky
Sky.
High and thank you God I'm
doing it telling. Gents.
This is whoever you are.
With. If you're interested
come to Room three
o two Baker Hotel. Hey wait
a minute. Don't
change empty still jump in. That was the
second movie burning down your boss.
You had em all wrong you never
crossed him. But you're
a guy who shoots person things afterward.
In your spot I'd almost choose the cops.
Even a first degree murder rap
is lucky I spotted you. As
a life giver being dead I want
to take care of a guy just
a little too smart take off the
net. And I don't like games.
That make it to be like you think he would
give it to me I remet down your route.
Let's wait until Paris the
chair against chamber just
a rope How do I know that like
you and me on the phone on
a level. You boys don't even sound the
same there really are when you put on
a mask. Who is bigger than the side maybe
you have too many questions are not going
to be answered. And I don't know
who I work with when we make
a split and who I think my
orders from get out of here.
I'll get. That choice you're
giving me you know the by no
means big or leave it. Should three
hundred grand for mine and at
least make it clear we're going my way home
I see the others where I'm at even when
we can split and I decide where and
when that takes place and makes it all
foolproof.
Thank you so. Now general
people to strike my coffee.
There are NO I do not stand before you to.
Get any wrong idea. I
don't sugar I give you
a check to show me how
high jar on the job.
Time lose it's only. That yes.
The police know you drove the
getaway car this time it's right
and no chance of parole. Is
time Tony go for life
under the hood that you
a criminal act with no chance of parole.
You don't have to tell me the school.
But no dames understand
no dates. Love friends.
If you don't like. It's dumb luck.
Tonight.
If you think I can't go on doing or nice
if I can spice it back I was tricked she
was so connected out. This job
you're talking about I said listen.
There are people are they killed when I
met Madge do you. I don't like heroes You
can tell like the warden
when they bring you.
Inside So I'm still listening.
Who has.
To watch what you.
Pass.
Is the description Max All units stand by
at one one seven attention all units one
one seven Here's a description of
a suspect involved in the armed robbery
of the shop West Bank remember match
wearing identical cover all having
a white delivery car belonging to the western
of all failed foreign. Law ships all
armed. The
path. Of
the the
.
Again a control issue
one one seven we have
a suspect or extract twenty injection they
wanted to have the come on come on get
out. Of one. Side you
know. Your pals have any ideas you'd
better strap sausage you're going off when
it's all going to watch you're crazy
there's nothing about flowers.
But you drop them off.
In the burning bring it in the main drop
and go around and never get in the way
they play. With what I'm going
to talk about. Or came up at
hand that's just what we're.
I don't know those cards.
I've got everything covered but in case
something does go wrong I can make
a pay off myself for Chrysler but then
a PRIOR to whatever I said with the money.
And the money when I think it had I'm
out of the crew. Right now is good enough
for me like the fourth year now when you
think if people had money every cabinet
spent that record I think my sense of the
man stays on or you don't. Add
and only because nobody can read on you.
You can't even read on each other that
you've never seen each other at those masses
and they just kept moving stupid and.
It's going to stay that way. Let me.
Get one of these for each other enough
money to keep you comfortable while you're
waiting but not enough to get into trouble
free energy to come in and maybe I can
stand on them to make up their mind
which way they're going to be.
To find tickets for where
you're going to reach going to
a different foreign country stay there so
I was aware and when they come and keep
those masks that we were going to pay
off this is where you get off that by.
Moving the door.
That you stopped as far as next to the
bank twice in the same morning so I was
there the woman who identified you was
a liar I was just telling the truth I did
and on the other with this is where your
truck or the getaway car they're telling
the truth to are wrong if I said anything
that it was
a robbery you want me to believe the
Dubica truck I want you know I want you
a frame then is that it. And if you spend
a penny one frame on that rap. Asked the
captain there he was the arresting officer
all real models. Just because I got to
jam over a gambling debt doesn't make me
a bank robber I watch
a lot about the truck. If I knew the answer
to that I wouldn't be here now for an
answer or one of the other
truck. Mr vendors here or the
insurance company is willing to give you
a break. In those we are same questions
same answers you can save your breath
it's my job Joe After all we've got to make
good the loss in fact we're willing to
pay out as much as twenty
five percent of the money as
a reward that's three hundred
thousand for Alito. You're industrial
engineer aren't you I never graduated
That's right that's cool and lives with the
engineers pretty good soldier to
Bronze Star Purple Heart try and buy
a cup of coffee with. Aim back to resume
his study that night why why I ask
myself what a man with
such training want to take
a job outside his line of attack for over
a million dollars That's why. I got the
job through the probation officer you can
ask. This because I have to give you any
trouble when I worked for you no not at
all but I'm afraid to let you go now I
think personally once and it's just that.
We sell to
a lot of very conservative people you
know our. Sergeant to this to call him
back go along with him some
questions I want to ask.
All right Ralph you want the hard way I
can fix that too you've got twenty years
staring you right in the face of your me
to say that I did it. Why don't you go
ahead Mr Martin you got
a big day tomorrow the boys will
help me keep prop company. Twenty
six my friend. I think the lesson
to me in the Far as I have
a confession is the first
thing in the morning.
With the back after person in the morning.
Make. Change.
Visitors again real.
Bride. Tenants.
Leap on the deep into flyers for half an
hour ago it was inside an abandoned movie
Bad still doesn't they're all in my
book is part of the job going to been
a huge truck as
a bomb goes away from the real getaway car
it could have been anything just give me
a little more time I'll switch on
a ride to check every movie
maybe. All right we can go sorry
we had to take. Us these.
Thanks. Juan.
Maybe you didn't hear
what I said. I said that.
Right. If. You.
Can only.
Keep.
Going to do it Rick. You don't understand
Rick. I noticed my Korean Rick what you
got to help Joe. Rick. Rick.
Lazio I think get you something
yeah to think. That information
was. Politically. The
first one as easy. As.
I got to know me. And yes
come. Dealing with it.
So I'm only like you when I got close look
at you spent three weeks no charge no I
don't. Think it is you you know so.
I get another cup of coffee.
And come back.
I gotta find
a way to clear myself
sometimes. So. Look I
want to know who framed me.
But only Willow. And ideas.
Naming. The intermixing and. Eight
hours. We are at. I want to.
Crap game. Anything else. Get real.
You won't have any
trouble. Follow the chain.
Which time.
Thank goodness and given even James.
May have been it will be easy you'll.
Be able to put a good diet I don't give
a relation to one of. Them Is this
a dice table but. All I get really
good legal much like in the state of.
Something is the load of methadone I
will show you when he said I'd give.
It Up. I don't put your. Eyes on the back.
So why.
Do the other.
But at. Any other spots
she's in Europe I usually.
Stop. To think.
Thanks. Everybody and I can't get
my. Night gown and he's coming out.
Anyone away with
a pole trying not unite but. Come on I'm
going to step on the feet to Colin except
for the big and out of all not that I'm not
on any practice over TIL THE END QUOTE
You know you know that
there's this town. Around
a big mess Foxconn I take sign and
again sign Man man I want that
one makes up for all of em one chance
when they don't get them and I.
Write the same. Thing I mean those
nights misspent and I'm not affording.
That makes nine money. To
Uganda the good point by me.
The way you. Cover the.
Mine was on top of the. Issue
is coming out on it right right
oh yeah I will jump down anyone away with
seven thank me and sign the outside I
want to tell you what it
was ten thirty Phillip.
Island when.
I. Get I'm.
Out. Of the simplest way. To.
Be too small right. So I'm busy.
My guy. Keeps coming up. I want to.
Thank you very well and. Your mind. Did
All right you seem to be in too much of
a very. Big. Since you.
Can't.
Watch. Me Now.
But. You've been giving
me that we shall night.
Sit back and I. Think that's sick. And
stop mashing time. It's
a rest. If
.
You. Look due to like.
You want to talk you are. Just a teacher
a man and that kind of trouble I don't know
what you're talking about. Because. You
look in the past you know this
find. You got the wrong guy.
When you read it so you got
me wrong but it was your Ph.
You know Will.
You. Or one of much I don't know
what you're talking about. This ng
my bike I got it out of the car I.
Just plain taken why it was so
interesting about us. Always start all
over again. But I do
like your talking about.
I can open you up maybe the cops can.
Come. So you were one of the
gang I had and the reason
I'm interested in this one. Plane
weighs in fifteen minutes pay you're
not going to be on.
The brunt of. That wire mean three
hundred grand to me. Who set it up
I don't. Look. We didn't have nothing
against you we didn't even know you
just feel that way Lucky me who else was
in on it I don't know that either but we
all form
a format about their only pray
three in the big guy. Gotta give
it to you straight that's the way
it was planned we all did it it was
a mess he didn't know I was never good
only I'm good none of us could squeal that
way if one of his didn't go away. I
think explains everything with that.
I will know what that
means like you. Will find
together. A big man sent me in
on this so we split five way.
Here. If I don't place pliant way there's
going to be no split at all. OK.
Go ahead and tell Sylvia Blake you're right
so I'm moving blind but I got you for
a birthday to point the way as we go along
you bring get even I don't know the make
guy so I'm takin
a chance. Remember I'm taking no chances
with human tween here and Bharat
partners. We don't want to miss our point.
Fortunately. Not of the
foreign buyers are serious
main the mission thing you can understand
the border line you go. By the I know
why I.
Checked for us said just that time you
make connections from what others make the
city center the area around to.
One way of United you know.
By the who's here. By the
cigarette machine to meet him.
As P.
Harris. Go ahead raise. Don't
worry about this boy. Stay
here.
I don't get very privileged to eat our
exchange on this man for the murder.
I said he's trying to say
about the. Debate. Never got
a chance B.
But you are clean he's right tell us about
adult. Who's down here with you can't do
it bitch when we come. In you
want to challenge you haven't got
a chance. With the.
Money not with us or working out of the.
Middle of that somebody down here with
a job like that because there is
the ambulance would be here once.
But don't be. Stupid.
Time's running out tell us.
A dance.
And you have. To forget your clean
tricks and you to make it is
a more deeply. Thanks.
Jim let's just win the.
Little piece. Of My Life.
One of the I have to go. Back because of
me my past midnight ing every crack made
it today is going to rain finally hang up
now and we feel cool af then everyone can
go outside and play Wendy
up and have a. Plan as
a minimum. I figure handsome
thing you watch. Sexual like the
fact. That you want to
die it's not provide.
A condolence. Lesson books. And it's
costing us if you're looking for something
cheap. I get nothing but the
edge. Then shall I backed into
a nice package point. About
a nice package. To bring home
that said you know you used
a generous. Satchel B.N.
Aneta conduct. Charge.
The rest. Is in your. Class and.
They say she's
a Jew the smartest girl that ever worked
for. The twelve times here sold it and the
process you conducted an epic
The second a quarter give
a fifty percent commission. Which
eventually. Came here yesterday.
Going to come into being
a two hours another mechanism on the money
because you don't buy the check mark why
not. Right that's not the
one thing I am not. That A.
Little I get outside telling
the like. Asking our
first. But everybody so gloomy
about the way that she's so
uncertain about the states or having
blizzards. If something like that with only
happened here but now that sunshine
and people catching fish and
just once
a fish what. That's possible to muscle
all depends on the fate of their first
came to do was to gain a grade of it
should be and coming down every season for
a good many years that I get
a back good to raise it. Was almost.
Thank you when you go to try and
some of this fishing Mr Amano.
There's. And that's because you can
do that and if he has to even.
Come early and bring
a lot of money. I
get him. That she's got. Me looking
in the pink. How she is a
big girl now preparing for
a bar exam Bill I already did and you since
anyone seen you around your past Yeah
two years one month and
a day since I got my walking papers. Still
didn't attempt. To spend twenty years
your life being
a crap and then get thrown out What am I
supposed to do stand up and shoot I mean
it was time to get out you can do fracture
health coverage for three times. All
right Scott Horsley time. Get back from
party and faster so now we got ourselves
a new boy I call
a friend well whatever it was you've been
through it and only memories. How about
an urgent telegram to me to hear how when
you're going on it's. Likely no way.
You must be hearing probably from the front
office on that one. You know the have.
Every bank in the country is on the alert
spot the serial number that was built and
up to now not one of Mr and. I think.
How would I like to find oil in my backyard
I don't know but I might be able to
deliver it going to you wouldn't fool enough
friend might be anything and again it
could be just what you're
looking for. I've been watching
a couple of strange characters tripped in
here one of the time. Came in anything to
hate here I want to imprint jewelry
store. And when I censor the work who
else a prize package by the name of Tony
room. Should turn into a trance like
a bank job. Printing and I think oh no
it's. Going to crap because by so I was
supposed to be free of them as well because
for me since very much still around
that time then anything else. The talk
is about the money spent big money
trying to come out of the West Bank
check last week break they get together
and what their next right
into and. How do we handle
a temp. Keep out of sight like order the
bottom line of the police. We're going to
reach
a donation now thanks to him. Any idea
how much reward this will bring him
down which should be pretty twenty five
percent of what the insurance companies
stand to lose and that's over a quarter of
a million. Actual run of money and
you're the cuff agent was played out.
Given the of the unit and you.
Feel like it.
I know the time but trust implied
this is not a spec to accomplish not
a Mustang tearing up
a new thing moving people. Take it you can't
deal with cost basis in you're out of
the Senate I just think.
You are from do you want to make your
signal I have and that is just silly things
that. Come up then they make you know the
details we can and I will show you which
bundle if you're. Feeling thanks
to the company My pleasure.
Not bad at all I mean by health
of the nation. I'm here for
a vacation bank and you can I. Tell me.
What you like to buy something you know I
have done so many things that back on.
Maybe. That especially. Coming out of.
The spam came here and that's not it
but it's not thanks. To Google got.
Family on the phone. You mean
here now. That I eat man.
Thanks. I asked Sam.
You know. You want to get about. Once
a vacation all those.
High well. Luck.
And I thought you were glad to see me you
know I'm always glad to see you I'm going
to come by. When you're doing my budget
a lot of studying to do I've got news
that important you have nothing more
important in your lot Sam's Surely you
are that's why I'm here you know being
a law student has a back. I thought
a brief and brought it to the mayor
my. Son just like you. Have the facts
right that that. I get the
commissioner to reopen your case.
You don't understand that it's
a chance for you to get back on. To I don't
want to go back on the force Oh no no
this is your daughter Helen don't me I know
what it meant to you being forced into
retirement through politics this is your
chance to come back you're not going to
let pride get in the way. Alright thanks
now you're going to turn right around and
go on with those books. And. That.
That I can like young man just
take his name is Pete hair.
Night. Vacation pay all my hair
like I won the money and I
will never let you sail. But the
way the hundred forty. Just
softened up. Right now we're playing them.
Just posted. Makes me.
Go ahead Peter.
Not roaming. Maybe your I bet
you couldn't. Check the.
Money but. Seconds. Before.
Submitting your. Past You know I had
it. Come on now I think I have.
It Down I get it back I
said so if you want. Me
and I have it we think that it
will all the time. And you're
a man or you lose all the time. And your
money he wanted more about question.
Morning you don't like that boys cannot
afford to school me on the covers and some
plant dynamite daughter want me about
a promise to be careful. And
a man should never press bad luck.
Expect be around this time one.
Way from. Cancer the original. Is not girl
spoke. But I see.
By skins just bring in
the suckers and then.
Make
a kind of. Civil in me.
It's like it's. Always
room for one more Tony.
Around. Me and I figure
you about ten hours in
a clearing so we're. Going to take
a walk to the beach before I turn it so
what's the best to be out of town without
even seeing the net is there I
think it's come back some other.
Super newbie is not ever. Going
to back up again. Soon with.
The National.
The.
Higher.
I do trust my child. I didn't mean.
Baby you meant to give me the
office when you got that car in the tape.
That's what you chose. To be sure before
I cracked go on. Don't take
no big thinking if you're
a couple of guys like passing this bill on
a vacation. And just go in for my one.
I call and. You must be one of the
guys in the van. We were inside doing
a drive. Sorry
the rough you are. So I feel.
I've done the same in your style. One
will get you tend to get the other guy
uncovered to.
Do more to be. Just like.
Three hundred smacked before
you get to where you name it.
We don't even know is what would know where
to find him didn't show up so why would
he bring us here again let me. I don't
like working for someone I don't know
specially he can recognise me and I
can't organize him neither do I.
Came. Really just
a big. Gum chewing character. I
think it's myself the.
TIME How do you make that you more hands
on your part it would break me down say I
didn't want you to write I gave in the
morning. And that's why I asked to go I
don't understand about man. He worked hard
all year and nothing to talk about your
vacation and would cause you to endorse
and fight hard. For you know that
a lot of things don't thank you. I
printed. Out For instance what you do on
your. I save up to play cards.
I guess I should go along
a deck of cards instead of us moving since
I say you did the right thing. You can
swim to the mike you play can I tell you
what I'm going to the pool tomorrow
morning if you mean if you could be
a. This.
Right thanks.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. So.
Warning on it. You always bring
a book along when you have
a date why did they. Say. No to the
state of Missouri. That's why
she's on cramming for the.
Now cracked. County are opposed
to the higher education
even. Though it's just that you
don't look. The lawyer for me.
I found people really like
that they said Take yourself
a. Look at you let's say you are probably
a combination of extend
it up Leigh. Sales.
My concern ourselves with luck I don't
want to but to get than to spike up the
seven nations. I've always heard the
best witnesses the ones who want to.
Change the game time. It's more for you and
for free to always arrange to have your
cases tried in front of all
male juries. You can't lose. A
U.V.
To some promising guess. I
left my cigarettes of the
camera on the right track.
I meant to pass.
The test.
Want to misquote there. Are two cards
and I kept going to them again with
a lawyer you may never get to be one of the
chest deep sometimes wanted to join it
so I took
a few. Yep
. Hear what he said
Elsie. My point in Syria.
We're still.
Thinking here she now. She.
Is cooperate. What is this.
My player wants to know what
is this what your line is to.
Me for it. I don't like.
It.
And point it for you. He
needed to stick at it.
And make sure. Now we're going to take
a nice way. To get to
the right place to tell
a story if you might. I don't. Know.
When it comes and I. Might
buy once again quite.
I mean. Oh. Yeah I didn't know you had
visited him at all right
Ali. This was all straw man.
Came I see Mr. Hundreds
to. It which took me
to taking a walk with
him. I explained we had
a date and what I don't want I told. Just
a couple of nature. We were
chatting about what you. Have. Been
a very warm discussion. Oh I.
Just got into into this to you.
Thanks. I hardly missed. I only carry.
This in airs. At eight
only. I know a sure cure for
a nosebleed. A cold night
in the middle of the back.
And yes. Playful. I.
Don't mind making it but he still buys
any. I thought the laws of the man was
innocent until proven guilty that's right.
And so bring the circumstantial evidence
. My attorney how would you advise me to
answer. I cannot answer No unless you can
answer honestly. My time.
Giving me some good advice.
Thanks. Free speech.
Was.
One of the.
Before for so long I don't whether that
means the whole thing no kidding there's
nothing for you I have a right
there for you. She sounds like
a business one. That I have.
Or the problem. With. David is
that we're not going to
fight back this. Thing in
a manner and that I'm telling you.
He's fine she also sounds like
a business mind. And
it's been for years and
yet an. Airhead American.
Male from home. Is always. Expects
you to give him some silent study
tonight. Alison that night.
Of the most right for that.
Man's question.
Not even looking after anything else. And
only an emetic. Every. An excellent.
Guy. With the best back twenty.
Or so you got your invitation
tell me. About your friend.
To get used to. The West.
Is not. Going to make. You
sound scary but you're
concerned I'm always.
Going to forget. But you
done. It do you.
Pick.
Up the gun while keep the seat sounds.
And know our. Going.
To. Happen.
Up in the well to let me tell you. A No.
Every.
Right. Now you can listen
to me like you want to and.
I got my invitation the party I take
parish you gave them that will show
you got it wrong a cap
space bought by gambling
a man puts up his bet he's entitled
to be paid he wins ours last but if
you put
a. Possible twenty years and. You're
looking guy who was kind to the child
that's why I'm putting myself in what you
like and that. Might apply on me and not
. On everybody. In the green or smart
guy but it happens when Mr Big sees.
You two boys make my friends go to sleep.
In case you get any ideas about
this again later. I sleep
like.
I can look into you. Cannot or principal
Mr Hassel I just don't like anybody
running around twice the same day. I
tell you you don't have to make up any
stories for me that's
right you do. Peek I know
anybody who does something I
shouldn't but. The way I am in
a kid out always the one asking
questions. But you can cross examine.
It out as not at the time I thought they'd
get off. On I can't help feeling you're
in trouble. And I could benefit
when you stop this crash. I'm
new to Pete I've been on top long enough
to tempt you tricks of the trade. Those
playmates of you is a pretty obvious.
I think out on your one question at
a time. Especially in class which you
picked up on my father's retired captain of
police. A city that explains your being
a lawyer dopamine is when you
free of of the fact that W.
You're
a nice girl but in case you're thinking
of mothering me forget it I'm no straight
talk you can take up an
I like my neck without
a collar gets lost. Now
I'm supposed to be hurt
maybe you can cry but. I think you're in
trouble now I'm going to help us to stay
together Mind your own business.
And if.
You get
a task that. They need out on the
boat tomorrow Don for the split I
went out on the police on to your light
signal then I moved. Into my seat first.
Miss Don't worry. I won't.
I'm going. To be asleep by this time.
Problem. Pretty often when you were young
you. Always knew in something that
struck me as. Fact kind of mission when
a very. Very tough some little trinket
you wanted money for the movies.
To get in the first form and you both
came down with me just. To get myself.
Once even wanted to know him and get
a new model look at you.
Know we were able to work.
Around about half step
machete. I got to tell you
to take my advice. And those days you would
have gone running after him if I asked
him that too. How much
additional. Way you'll be happy.
Professional interest. The name of Dan
something's happened I know it sounds
crazy in
a logical but. The way it is.
He's out of bounds we were
way out of bounds he said that before why
isn't that enough and I tell you not this
time all right. He's an
ex-con. I want to hit you
over the head with. What else to know
about him isn't that enough no it's not
there's more there's got to be more it
would be so positive if there weren't
something. Put out if you got against him
going home tonight young lady in fact the
way you solve my problems when I was a
kid this is for your own good it was
a leave me to leave me punk and
go home and forget him. You can
start the ball rolling on that
rehearing I'll be. Allied.
I am not passing out.
I am.
Wanting. To tell you boys are going
fishing so yeah we'll see you get such
a kick out of it we decided to give it a
turn sport my way in a pick me give him
a. Good coach Sebastian.
Might as well take
a song see the three of us are
going. To read about. This
photo that manage.
The I am. I am the stand your
next campaign the police
because I am a long time ago.
It will be able to match
a star in the man. Pictures.
I don't. Get out.
Luckily all of them do
a pretty good everywhere. But
. Thanks.
Ali.
But goes it is still that.
It's
a matter of relative. Lead. But
quite. A proposition I
know where the money is.
As shown to. Be
a sound. I can make up to call at.
Two hundred thousand pounds Tommy
I kept me in to. Be here when.
I got the take for always
will have to. Sober.
Up I have to begin. By split with Kate.
Because.
They.
Might see ways. I live in it
all the time like me needs to.
Get.
Back back up. And get it
we'll just take it easy to get here. The
foreman out of the split. You get around
a lot. But in my job.
Making out like in all
depends on what is signed
and calls for you never had
a chance we had that big guy in the
beginning. Don't let that bother you Tony it
was all Mark Anyway we
should have. That's right.
The name is eight. Thanks and Peter
was that was shot and killed until.
Something I think Joe Yeah. The only
person who would not be there as was in
Tijuana would be the one sent
in there to hide out for
a while. You're a boy with
a lot of ideas. Like only a
couple No you couldn't use
a million tonight cash but
you could trade it in for
a nice clean reward. But
I don't figure. That
one down to. Your being there
to give us a lift the money on
a platter I need for the big sack
Captain Forster they were sure.
We would look after I. Try my story
on the side. If I'm wrong. I'll
apologize.
Again. Sometimes.
We raise which George. Allen can find.
Their next tires. You get
a break come. Jan
what have you heard. What's
wrong doing here. And save.
Surprise when. Mrs Levy turned the trick.
Didn't come off the way
we planned it. It's.
Time to.
Forget was T.V.'s.
Turned out to on. Skype.
Anybody surgery ward. It's
jammed. Into it after.
Every show. Thanks.
I know it's just hard now Helen but I feel
the loss of your father is keenly as you
do I don't know lots of what he did. If
there's anything that you ever need when
you call and. Thanks to.
All one other thing.
About. He's a fine boy
that's great he got into
a long time ago is more than made up for
it in the way I feel my company will
underwrite him any time. I
tried so hard to. Get it out
the last thing he said was
for Joe to give you is for.
Taking. Time to get over the shock. He
rolls metal isn't enough when you're
along. Pretty close. I told
her about you which is.
Why don't you ask her.
Again.